{
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "title": "week2",
        "questions": [
          {
            "index": 1,
            "question": "Which of these is not a pillar of sustainability?",
            "options": ["Environmental sustainability", "Economic sustainability", "Trans-boundary sustainability", "Social sustainability"],
            "correct": "Trans-boundary sustainability"
          },
          {
            "index": 2,
            "question": "The Trinity explosion of 1945 is taken as the beginning of the",
            "options": ["Holocene", "Cenocene", "Anthropocene", "Eocene"],
            "correct": "Anthropocene"
          },
          {
            "index": 3,
            "question": "According to Malthusian model,",
            "options": [
              "Population grows in geometric progression, food supply increases in arithmetic progression",
              "Population grows in geometric progression, food supply increases in geometric progression",
              "Population grows in arithmetic progression, food supply increases in arithmetic progression",
              "Population grows in arithmetic progression, food supply increases in geometric progression"
            ],
            "correct": "Population grows in geometric progression, food supply increases in arithmetic progression"
          },
          {
            "index": 4,
            "question": "The demographic transition sees a society move from",
            "options": [
              "High birth rate, low death rate to low birth rate, high death rate",
              "Low birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, low death rate",
              "High birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, low death rate",
              "High birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, high death rate"
            ],
            "correct": "High birth rate, high death rate to low birth rate, low death rate"
          },
          {
            "index": 5,
            "question": "Which of these is a pillar of sustainability?",
            "options": ["Social sustainability", "Industrial sustainability", "Agricultural sustainability", "Trans-boundary sustainability"],
            "correct": "Social sustainability"
          },
          {
            "index": 6,
            "question": "Which of these is a preventive check according to Malthus?",
            "options": ["Foresight", "Vice", "Misery", "Flood"],
            "correct": "Foresight"
          },
          {
            "index": 7,
            "question": "The quantum of human impacts can be written as",
            "options": ["I = P + A + T", "I = P X A + T", "I = P X A X T", "I = P + A X T"],
            "correct": "I = P X A X T"
          },
          {
            "index": 8,
            "question": "The book 'An Essay on the Principle of Population' was written by",
            "options": ["Darwin", "Malthus", "Spencer", "Owens"],
            "correct": "Malthus"
          },
          {
            "index": 9,
            "question": "The logistic growth equation curve is",
            "options": ["I-shaped", "J-shaped", "S-shaped", "U-shaped"],
            "correct": "S-shaped"
          },
          {
            "index": 10,
            "question": "Which of these is a positive check according to Malthus?",
            "options": ["Late marriage", "War", "Celibacy", "Moral restraint"],
            "correct": "War"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }